JARED TANKSLEY

PREMIER SERVICE CONSULTANT

CONTACT INFORMATION

• **Phone:** 405-385-2795

• E-Mail: Jared.Tanksleyl@gmail.com

• Github: Jaredtanksley

 Address: 10708 Glover River Drive Yukon, OK 73099

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration - Entrepreneurship Oklahoma State University - Stillwater, OK

Minor in Accounting 24 Credit Hours Needed for Bachelor's Degree Oklahoma State University - Stillwater,

Full Stack Web Developer Nanodegree Udacity (September 2021)

ACCOLADES

AP Scholar Fall 2010

Dean's ListFall 2011

Harry and Maxine Weise Scholarship Fall 2012 & 2013

Choctaw Nation Higher Education Scholarship

2010-2013

CERTIFICATIONS

- AT&T Technical Knowledge Test II
 2019
- Smith Defensive Driving
- ACT National Career Readiness Gold 2015

ABOUT ME

Detailed oriented, self-motivated, and performance driven individual that adapts to new situations and environments quickly. I enjoy being a leader to my peers and helping others to succeed. Also, I strive to become the expert in every situation, and I'm extremely proficient in computer, networking, and cloud-based technologies as well as Microsoft Office.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Premier Service Consultant

AT&T/Work From Home/July 2021 - Current

- Participate in a sales-driven workplace requiring monthly quotas to be obtained in a highly interactive environment.
- Required to set daily objectives and self-manage in a virtual work from home space.
- Collaborate with peers and customers on troubleshooting mobility technical, billing, and order issues.
- Provide and coach customers based on information from various computer systems to work towards a common resolution as well as relaying new information to help other agents.
- Heavily research detailed promotional or technical information to quickly provide an accurate response or resolution.

Wire Technician

AT&T/Oklahoma City, OK/November 2015 - July 2021

- Test, verify, and repair a broad range of AT&T video services, copper cable internet, and fiber optic internet into a customer premises while providing and communicating information and education.
- Negotiated various contract modifications, followed-up and explained quotations, revisions, and conditions with customers in a collaborative manner.
- Handled business invoicing and billing as well as the planning and analysis of the procurement function for materials.
- Preformed and completed job assignments based on reading data from telecommunication blueprints and orders.
- Assigned as a duty supervisor on the weekend for over a year to coach, mentor, and supervise other technicians and train DirecTV managers on U-Verse management responsibilities.
- Maintained continuous top performance metrics for over five years. Achieved top technician in every major measured category for all of the Oklahoma City metro area in 2018.

Shipping Coordinator/Documentation Specialist 180 Medical/Oklahoma City, OK/December 2014 - November 2015

- Initially worked as a liaison for the shipping warehouse and sales specialist to review, communicate, and distribute important documentation for shipping as well as addressing general shipping and logistics information.
- Promoted within six months to a documentation specialist; named a top performer in accuracy and total amount of document processing first month out of training.
- Worked with HIPAA privacy laws and utilized Microsoft Word, Access, and Excel on a daily basis as well as internet-based database and informational systems.
- Consulted with third-party insurance agents to provide accurate insurance information for patents and obtain detailed information to meet patient needs. Verified extremely complex insurance information.